<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ISRC on Lynkify Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/isrc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ISRC on Lynkify Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 16:55:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/isrc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UPC vs ISRC: Unraveling the Codes of the Music Industry</title>
      <link>/posts/upc-vs-isrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 16:55:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/upc-vs-isrc/</guid>
      <description>UPC vs ISRC: Unraveling the Codes of the Music Industry In the intricate realm of music, identification and organization play a pivotal role in ensuring seamless distribution, tracking, and royalty management. Two essential codes, UPC and ISRC, stand as gatekeepers to this organized world, each serving a distinct purpose in the music ecosystem.
UPC: The Mark of Physical Products UPC Code
Universal Product Code, commonly known as UPC, is a 12-digit barcode that serves as a unique identifier for physical products, including CDs, DVDs, and vinyl records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover ISRC Search by Lynkify: Find ISRC of Your Music</title>
      <link>/posts/discover-isrc-search-by-lynkify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/discover-isrc-search-by-lynkify/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: For music creators, the International Standard Recording Code (ISRC) holds the key to seamless music management, royalty collection, and global recognition. With Lynkify&amp;rsquo;s revolutionary ISRC Search tool, discovering and utilizing ISRC codes has never been easier. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the significance of ISRC codes and how Lynkify empowers music creators to streamline their music journey.
The Importance of ISRC Codes for Music Creators: ISRC codes act as unique fingerprints for your sound recordings.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
