<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UPC on Lynkify Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/upc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UPC on Lynkify Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 16:55:06 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/upc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UPC vs ISRC: Unraveling the Codes of the Music Industry</title>
      <link>/posts/upc-vs-isrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 16:55:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/upc-vs-isrc/</guid>
      <description>UPC vs ISRC: Unraveling the Codes of the Music Industry In the intricate realm of music, identification and organization play a pivotal role in ensuring seamless distribution, tracking, and royalty management. Two essential codes, UPC and ISRC, stand as gatekeepers to this organized world, each serving a distinct purpose in the music ecosystem.
UPC: The Mark of Physical Products UPC Code
Universal Product Code, commonly known as UPC, is a 12-digit barcode that serves as a unique identifier for physical products, including CDs, DVDs, and vinyl records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Power of Music with Lynkify&#39;s UPC Finder</title>
      <link>/posts/find-upc-with-lynkify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 16:22:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/find-upc-with-lynkify/</guid>
      <description>Dive into a realm where music meets seamless identification. Lynkify introduces its groundbreaking UPC Finder, transcending the boundaries between physical and digital musical landscapes.
Effortless UPC Discovery Bid farewell to the era of searching through physical packaging. Lynkify&amp;rsquo;s UPC Finder effortlessly retrieves UPCs for both physical and digital music, ensuring accurate information always rests at your fingertips.
Elevate Your Musical Expedition Discover a profound connection with your music collection. By identifying UPCs, effortlessly locate songs on streaming platforms, monitor sales, and gain valuable insights into your musical journey.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
